Now, the
これで、少
Then take a break.
し 休憩を行います
1時間
the break
の 休憩
So, please limit your margins.
で、 余裕を抑えてください
I,
私 は、
I have many thoughts for you.
あ なたに多くのみの思いがあります
Wipe boasts a nostalgic feel for the welfare era.
ワ イ プ は、福祉の時代の懐かしさを誇っています
It means protecting your health.
健 康 を 守 る こと を 意 味 します
For me, health is powerful.
私 は、健康が威力はあります
Feels good
気持ち良い
...
Why is it getting worse?
なん でひどくなってきてるの?
Is this person safe?
この人、安心してるの?
Yeah, from where?
うん、どっから?
From where?
どっから?
Oh, where did it come from?
あ、どっから?
Oh, everywhere!
あ、あちこちだ!
There it was!
あったね!
Oh, you!
あ、おまえ!
why?
なん で?
You...
おまえ...
This way!
こっちだ!
That person is here!
あの人、こっちだ!
Yes, that's right!
うん、そうなんだ!
yes?
そう?
It's this way!
こっちだよ!
grandma
お ば あ ちゃん
Please take a break with me.
と 一緒に休憩してください
cute!
かわいい!
That's amazing!
すごいね!
You've gotten better!
上手になったね!
Are you getting better at it?
上手くなってきた?
cute!
かわいい!
Ah, it feels so good!
あ〜気持ちいい!
I love you
可愛す
Giru!
ぎ る!
可愛
stomach!
い!
Super good!
超 上手い!
You're very good at it!
超上手いね!
It's a complicated feeling!
複雑だな、気持ち!
It's complicated!
複雑だ!
Let's go!
行っちゃう!
Ah, this feels so good!
あ〜気持ちいいこれ!
amazing!
すごい!
go!
行く!
OK
行
Ku!
く!
Let's go!
行 っちゃう!
go!
行く!
amazing!
すごい!
Feels good!
気持ちいい!
go!
行く!
Feels good!
気持ちいい!
feeling
気持ち
good!
いい!
go!
行 く!
行く!
go!
行 く!
行く!
It feels really good!
本当に気持ちいい!
Feels good!
気持ちいい!
appear!
見える!
It's full!
いっぱい入ってる!